{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a protocol used to set up secure connections and exchange of cryptographic keys in IPsec VPNs?",
      "options": ["SSL", "IKE", "ESP", "DHE"],
      "correct_answers": ["IKE"]
    },
    {
      "question": "An access control model that enforces the strictest set of access rules is known as:",
      "options": ["MAC", "RBAC", "DAC", "ABAC"],
      "correct_answers": ["MAC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the acronyms listed below refers to a cryptographic software tool for secure email communication and data protection?",
      "options": ["DES", "PEM", "EFS", "PGP"],
      "correct_answers": ["PGP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of action allows an attacker to exploit the XSS vulnerability?",
      "options": ["Code injection", "Banner grabbing", "PIN recovery", "Input validation"],
      "correct_answers": ["Code injection"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A type of vulnerability where the state of a resource is verified at one point in time but may change before the resource is actually used is called:",
      "options": ["TOC", "TOC/TOU", "TOU", "TSIG"],
      "correct_answers": ["TOC/TOU"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The term \"SMS\" is used in reference to:",
      "options": ["Text messaging services", "Enhanced messaging services", "Multimedia messaging services", "Rich communication services"],
      "correct_answers": ["Text messaging services"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following terms refers to a framework and knowledge base that provides understanding of TTPs used during cyberattacks?",
      "options": ["CVSS", "ATT&CK", "TAXII", "STIX"],
      "correct_answers": ["ATT&CK"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a security solution that provides the capability for detection, analysis, response, and real-time monitoring of cyber threats at the device level?",
      "options": ["SWG", "CASB", "EDR", "NGFW"],
      "correct_answers": ["EDR"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a system containing mappings of domain names to various types of data, such as numerical IP addresses?",
      "options": ["TCP/IP", "DNS", "SQL", "DHCP"],
      "correct_answers": ["DNS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The term \"OTA\" refers to the process of wirelessly transmitting data, updates, or information to electronic devices, such as smartphones, tablets, or IoT devices, typically using cellular networks, Wi-Fi, or other wireless communication methods.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the acronyms listed below refers to a piece of hardware and associated software/firmware designed to provide cryptographic and key management functions?",
      "options": ["EFS", "HSM", "SFC", "TPM"],
      "correct_answers": ["HSM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a PUP? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "A type of computer program not explicitly classified as malware by AV software",
        "An application downloaded and installed without the user's consent",
        "A type of software that may adversely affect the computer's security and performance, compromise user's privacy, or display unsolicited ads",
        "An application downloaded and installed with the user's consent",
        "A type of computer program explicitly classified as malware by AV applications",
        "A type of free, utility software often bundled with a paid app"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "A type of computer program not explicitly classified as malware by AV software",
        "A type of software that may adversely affect the computer's security and performance, compromise user's privacy, or display unsolicited ads",
        "An application downloaded and installed with the user's consent"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "A measure of the likelihood that a biometric security system will incorrectly reject an access attempt by an authorized user is referred to as:",
      "options": ["FAR", "CER", "CRC", "FRR"],
      "correct_answers": ["FRR"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following enables the automation of vulnerability scanning and compliance checking?",
      "options": ["SAML", "OVAL", "SCAP", "SASE"],
      "correct_answers": ["SCAP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the acronyms listed below refers to a comprehensive strategy and set of procedures designed to ensure that an organization can continue its critical operations and functions during and after a disruptive event?",
      "options": ["BIA", "SLE", "BCP", "BPA"],
      "correct_answers": ["BCP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Given the computational limitations of IoT devices, smartcards, and mobile devices, which of the following digital signature algorithms would be the most efficient choice due to its smaller key size and lower computational requirements?",
      "options": ["RSA", "ECDHE", "DSA", "ECDSA", "ECC"],
      "correct_answers": ["ECDSA"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of software is used to prevent, detect, and remove malware from computer systems and networks?",
      "options": ["IDS", "SaaS", "AV", "WAF"],
      "correct_answers": ["AV"]
    },
    {
      "question": "An estimate based on the historical data of how often a threat would be successful in exploiting a vulnerability is known as:",
      "options": ["ALE", "SLA", "ARO", "SLE"],
      "correct_answers": ["ARO"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a rule-based access control mechanism associated with files and/or directories?",
      "options": ["EFS", "FACL", "FIM", "NTFS"],
      "correct_answers": ["FACL"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a DNS TXT record that allows the owner of a domain to specify all the servers authorized to send mail from their domain?",
      "options": ["DKIM", "SRV", "CNAME", "SPF"],
      "correct_answers": ["SPF"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a cryptographic method used to verify that a message or data has remained unaltered during transmission and originates from an authorized source?",
      "options": ["MAC", "CBC", "PEM", "GCM"],
      "correct_answers": ["MAC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a network security technology designed to monitor WLANs for unauthorized access, security threats, and suspicious activities?",
      "options": ["UTM", "WIDS", "NGFW", "WAF"],
      "correct_answers": ["WIDS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the acronyms listed below refers to a client-server protocol that provides centralized AAA services for remote-access users?",
      "options": ["OAuth", "RADIUS", "LDAP", "OpenID"],
      "correct_answers": ["RADIUS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of software enables centralized administration of mobile devices?",
      "options": ["MFA", "MMC", "MDM", "MFD"],
      "correct_answers": ["MDM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following defines a file format for storing and exchanging personal identity information, including private keys and digital certificates?",
      "options": ["P10", "P11", "P12", "P13"],
      "correct_answers": ["P12"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a cryptographic key exchange protocol that leverages ECC for enhanced security and efficiency?",
      "options": ["IKE", "ECDHE", "DHE", "ECDSA"],
      "correct_answers": ["ECDHE"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The term \"MTTF\" refers to a metric that represents the average amount of time a device or system is expected to operate before experiencing its first failure.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "In modern OSs, this feature prevents malicious code from executing in certain memory regions intended for data.",
      "options": ["DEP", "ECB", "DLP", "CRC"],
      "correct_answers": ["DEP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following enables the exchange of information between computer programs?",
      "options": ["API", "UI", "Device drivers", "SDK"],
      "correct_answers": ["API"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A cloud computing service model offering remote access to applications based on monthly or annual subscription fee is called:",
      "options": ["PaaS", "SaaS", "IaaS", "DaaS"],
      "correct_answers": ["SaaS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "RTBH is a type of DDoS attack.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which AES key length provides the highest level of security?",
      "options": ["128-bit key", "192-bit key", "256-bit key", "320-bit key"],
      "correct_answers": ["256-bit key"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a specific type of ICS?",
      "options": ["SoC", "CVSS", "SCADA", "RTOS"],
      "correct_answers": ["SCADA"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The MIME specification extends the email message format beyond simple text, enabling the transfer of graphics, audio, and video files over the Internet mail system. S/MIME is an enhanced version of the MIME protocol that enables email security features by providing encryption, authentication, message integrity, and other related services.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which part of the IPsec protocol suite provides authentication and integrity?",
      "options": ["CRC", "AH", "SIEM", "AES"],
      "correct_answers": ["AH"]
    }
  ]
}